

About Me

Front End Developer with Two years of experience in Responsive pixel perfect web design and Web apps. My greatest strength is quick learn, Hard work, Willing to learn new tech and everything i learned from free Source like w3schools, youtube FreeCodeCamp, etc...

Contact









+91 9943567950

manthonysuresh@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-m1995/

363, South street, Elaynkanni, Thandrampet, Tiruvannamalai, Tamil Nadu - 606753

Education

2013 - 2017

Completed B.E Mechanical Eng., in Mahendra Engineering College, Namakkal with CGPA 8.23

2011 - 2012

Completed HSC in Carmel Hrs. Sec. School, Elayankanni with 79.8%

2009 - 2010

Completed SSLC in Carmel Hrs. Sec. School, Elayankanni with 74%

Anthony M Front End Developer



https://anthonym995.github.io/portfolio/

Experience

FRONT END DEVELPOER - AUG 2021 - MAR 2022

Billionapps Infotech Solutions/Chennai - Developing pixel perfect responsive web design & web application, Converting Adobe XD, Figma design to web application and API intergration.

FRONT END DEVELOPER - JULY 2020 - JULY 2021

Itechuniversal/Chennai - Developing pixel perfect responsive web design and web application, Bootstrap, ¡Query, Git, Adobe Xd.

Professional Skills



Additional Skills

| Linux Distro | MongoDB | Express.js | Tailwind |
|--------------|------------|------------|-----------|
| Less/Scss | Git,GitHub | AdobeXd | MS Excell |

Hobbies

Playing Chess Rubik's Cube Mobile Games **Listening Songs**

Personal details

28/05/1995 Marital Status: Married Date of Birth :

Father's Name: Magimainathan Mother's Name: Francismary

: Tamil, English, Hindi Languages